<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
 <ModMetaData>
	<name>Vanilla Furniture Expanded - Architect</name>
	<author>Oskar Potocki, xrushha, legodude17, ISOREX</author>
	<url></url>
    <supportedVersions>
		<li>1.3</li>
	</supportedVersions>
	<packageId>VanillaExpanded.VFEArchitect</packageId>
	<description>Vanilla Furniture Expanded - Architect has been on my mind for a very long time. I always download every single mod adding new floors or fences, but I quickly become buried under all the new options, and eventually get pissed off because some of those options don't exactly fit Vanilla game in my eyes.
	
	I want new carpet colors, but I don't want all RGB hues - I want a small, tailored selection that fits the game. I want new tiles and floors, but I don't want 100 different patterns that have no distinction between them other than the looks. I want new fences, but I don't want more fence types than there are floor types. I want less, but I want more significant!
	
	Thus, Architect Expanded was born. Not only does it add new walls, fences, floors and carpets in various, vanilla-fitting colors, it also adds stone and metal bridges, as well as foundations that you can place on sand, so building in the desert will no longer be a problem! I seem to have forgotten to mention that wood now comes in 4 colors, all using just the base wood resource - so you can decide upon building what color your wooden objects will be!
	
	I really hope you will enjoy everything this mod has to offer, and it will allow you to make your colony at least twice as beautiful to look at.</description>
    <modDependencies>
        <li>
            <packageId>OskarPotocki.VanillaFactionsExpanded.Core</packageId>
            <displayName>Vanilla Expanded Framework</displayName>
            <steamWorkshopUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=2023507013</steamWorkshopUrl>
        </li>
    </modDependencies>
	<loadAfter>
		<li>OskarPotocki.VanillaFactionsExpanded.Core</li>
	</loadAfter>
 </ModMetaData>